Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/basak-tezcan-19194025 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Marketing Communications
Market Research
Public Relations

Basak Tezcan

Corporate Communications bei Facebook

Berlin Metropolitan Area

Summary

Located in Berlin I am an experienced communications professional with expertise in corporate communications, crisis and issues management, CSR and public affairs. Working for tech companies, having an intercultural background, being a working mom and a strong supporter of equal working and education opportunities, I believe that the digital transformation has the power to unlock neglected talents in societies - connect with me if that sounds interesting.

Experience

Facebook

Corporate Communications
November 2019 - Present (2 years 6 months)

Berlin, Berlin, Deutschland

Zalando SE

Senior Corporate Communications Manager May 2018 - November 2019 (1 year 7 months) Berlin Area, Germany

MSLGROUP

Consultant

December 2012 - April 2018 (5 years 5 months)

Berlin Area, Germany

United Parcel Service

Interactive Communications Specialist February 2011 - November 2012 (1 year 10 months)

Davies Meyer
Junior Consultant
February 2010 - July 2010 (6 months)

Suna & Inan Kirac Foundation Project Assistant February 2009 - November 2009 (10 months)

Deutsche Börse Student Marketing Assistant October 2006 - August 2007 (11 months)

Eurex Internship Marketing Communication April 2006 - September 2006 (6 months)

Bayerischer Rundfunk Internship February 2005 - March 2005 (2 months)

Education

Goldsmiths, University of London

MA Transnational Communication & GLobal Media, Media &

Communication · (2007 - 2008)

FH Würzburg
University Diploma, Communication-Design · (2002 - 2007)

Clavius Gymnasium Bamberg Abitur · (1992 - 2001)